
[
    {
      "question": "가다",
      "answer": "To go"
    },
    {
      "question": "오다",
      "answer": "To come"
    },
    {
      "question": "있다",
      "answer": "To have"
    },
    {
      "question": "이다",
      "answer": "To be"
    },
    {
      "question": "먹다",
      "answer": "To eat"
    },
    {
      "question": "마시다",
      "answer": "To drink"
    },
    {
      "question": "주다",
      "answer": "To give"
    },
    {
      "question": "보다",
      "answer": "To see"
    },
    {
      "question": "자다",
      "answer": "To sleep"
    },
    {
      "question": "일어나다",
      "answer": "To wake up or get up"
    },
    {
      "question": "사다",
      "answer": "To buy"
    },
    {
      "question": "쓰다",
      "answer": "To write or to use"
    },
    {
      "question": "웃다",
      "answer": "To laugh"
    },
    {
      "question": "울다",
      "answer": "To cry"
    },
    {
      "question": "입다",
      "answer": "To wear"
    },
    {
      "question": "걷다",
      "answer": "To walk"
    },
    {
      "question": "읽다",
      "answer": "To read"
    },
    {
      "question": "배우다",
      "answer": "To learn"
    },
    {
      "question": "공부하다",
      "answer": "To study"
    },
    {
      "question": "만나다",
      "answer": "To meet"
    }
  ]
  